Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000030; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000031; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000032; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000033; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000034; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000035; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000036; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000037; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000038; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000039; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000040; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000041; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000042; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000043; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000044; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000045; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000046; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000047; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000048; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000049; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000050; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000051; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000052; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000053; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000054; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000055; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000056; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000057; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000058; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000059; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000060; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000061; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000062; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000063; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000064; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000065; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000066; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Crime of Honor, 1971; ref222_000067; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 67)
- Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223; Nur al Dimirdash; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Music and Love and Spying, 1971; ref223_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 40, Folder 79)
- Without Pity, 1971; ref224; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Without Pity, 1971; ref224_000030; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225; Mustafa, Hossam Dine; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Al Shaimaa, 1972; ref225_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 58)
- The Anger, 1972; ref226; Anwar Shinawi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Anger, 1972; ref226_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - The Anger, 1972; ref226_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - The Anger, 1972; ref226_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - The Anger, 1972; ref226_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 62)
- Imtithaal, 1972; ref227; Al Imam, Hassan; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Imtithaal, 1972; ref227_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 41, Folder 72)
- The Lights, 1972; ref228; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - The Lights, 1972; ref228_000030; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Gang of Teenagers, 1973; ref229_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 51)
- Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Looking for a Scandal, 1973; ref230_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 62)
- So Long, Love, 1973; ref231; Salem, Atef; 1 Photographic Prints
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - So Long, Love, 1973; ref231_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 42, Folder 82)
- Devils Forever, 1974; ref232; Mahmoud Farid; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Devils Forever, 1974; ref232_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 43, Folder 12)